(Raj:)If you look carefully at Venus...
(Raj:)...you should be able to see
the International Space Station pass by.
(Lucy:)Wow, your friend was actually up there?
(Raj:)Yeah, he brought me back
a T-shirt that said:
"My Friend Went to the Space Station
and All I Got Was This Lousy T-shirt."
(Lucy:)Did he take the T-shirt to space?
(Raj:)Nope. It's exactly as lousy as advertised.
(Raj:)Speaking of friends,
they have been asking to meet you.
(Raj:)I was thinking maybe
we could all hang out sometime?
(Lucy:)I don't know, how many are there?
(Raj:)Let's see. Six.
(Raj:)That's pretty cool. I have six friends.
I'm kind of like Sinatra.
Six strangers, that's a lot of pressure.
(Lucy:)Staring at me, asking me
personal questions like, "What do you do?
(Lucy:)Where are you from? Why did you
lock yourself in the bathroom?"